<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Nook Farm Honey</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Nook Farm Honey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Nook Farm Honey™ is a small-scale producer of local Cumbrian wildflower honey and also sells speciality honeys. Helen Griggs, her husband Duncan, and their daughter Kate, keep their bees at Nook Farm and at other locations in the Bailey and Kielder Forest area of North Cumbria. Nook Farm is idyllic, surrounded by wildflowers and unspoilt countryside. Traditional farming methods encourage the growth of Clover, Dandelion, Meadowsweet, Thistles, Willowherb and many other native species essential to honey bees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy online</title>
      <link>/order/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/order/</guid>
      <description>Buy Online Pure Cumbrian Wildflower Honey Our Wildflower Honey is very runny, it is beautiful in flavour and to look at, it is truly the taste
 Sorry OUT of Stock
 Borage Flower Honey Borage Honey is a single flower honey and unique in its flavour and quality. It is a pale light runn
 £7.95
Add to Cart   Balsam Flower Honey Balsam Honey is amber coloured, it has a fairly thick consistency but will still run off a spoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faqs/</guid>
      <description>FAQs   How do I order some of your honey? Use our online ordering system. Alternatively you may wish to complete our order form. You can download a copy from the website. You may want to email us, our email address is info@nookfarmhoney.co.uk This email address is being protected from spam bots, you need Javascript enabled to view it and someone will contact you back. Alternatively you can give us a call or Fax on 016977 48317.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Links British Beekeepers Association www.britishbeekeepers.com
Honey Association www.honeyassociation.com
Hives Save Lives www.hivessavelives.com
Distinctly Cumbrian www.crea.co.uk/distinctly_cumbrian.htm
CraftsAndCo.com www.craftsandco.com
Artisan Food in Cumbria www.artisan-food.com
Near Howe Self Catering Accommodation www.nearhowe.co.uk
Bees in Art www.beesinart.com
Carpe Diem Gardens www.carpe-diem-gardens.co.uk
Sugar Free Recipes www.sugarfreerecipes.co.uk/home.htm
Bee Happy Plants www.beehappyplants.co.uk
Northern Jacob Sheep www.northernjacobsheep.co.uk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Honey</title>
      <link>/our-honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-honey/</guid>
      <description>Our Honey Our honey is treated with the upmost care from the time it leaves the beehive. We filter and bottle all our honey at Nook Farm. Our honey is just fine filtered to clean the honey, nothing is added or taken away. The filter we use still allows very small particles of beeswax and pollen to remain in the honey. We believe a finer filter would remove some of the taste and beneficial properties of the honey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stockists</title>
      <link>/stockists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stockists/</guid>
      <description>Stockists Download an order form or contact your local stockist
Abbey Bridge B&amp;amp;B (Lanercost Brampton )
Alston Whole Foods (Front Street, Alston, CA9 3QH )
Ashburton Village Store (21 Ashburton Road Gosforth NE3 4XN )
Beetham Nurseries (Pool Darkin Lane Milnthorpe LA7 7AP )
Bush Nook Guesthouse (Gilsland, Cumbria )
Cartmel Village Shop (The Square Cartmel Cumbria LA11 6QB )
Chestnut House (Finkle Street Pooley Bridge Penrith CA10 2NW )</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>