<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Nook Farm Honey</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Nook Farm Honey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Nook Farm Honey™ is a small-scale producer of local Cumbrian wildflower honey and also sells speciality honeys. Helen Griggs, her husband Duncan, and their daughter Kate, keep their bees at Nook Farm and at other locations in the Bailey and Kielder Forest area of North Cumbria. Nook Farm is idyllic, surrounded by wildflowers and unspoilt countryside. Traditional farming methods encourage the growth of Clover, Dandelion, Meadowsweet, Thistles, Willowherb and many other native species essential to honey bees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsam Flower Honey</title>
      <link>/balsam_flower_honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/balsam_flower_honey/</guid>
      <description>Balsam Flower Honey  Balsam Honey is amber coloured, it has a fairly thick consistency but will still run off a spoon. It has a very distinctive taste with a background flavour not dissimilar to toffee. Balsam Honey is wholesome and very satisfying you may not be able to resist eating it straight from the jar. It is a single flower honey, which is produced by Mahmoud a beekeeper based in Manchester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Borage Flower Honey</title>
      <link>/borage_flower_honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/borage_flower_honey/</guid>
      <description>Borage Flower Honey  Borage Honey is a single flower honey and unique in its flavour and quality. It is a pale light runny honey with a delicate mild taste. We work closely with Mark who keeps bees in Yorkshire and supplies us with Borage Honey. Borage honey is a very versatile honey and can be used to sweeten tea or coffee. It adds flavour and sweetness without overpowering other tastes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy online</title>
      <link>/order/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/order/</guid>
      <description>Buy Online Pure Cumbrian Wildflower Honey Our Wildflower Honey is very runny, it is beautiful in flavour and to look at, it is truly the taste of Cumbria.
 Sorry OUT of Stock  Borage Flower Honey Borage Honey is a single flower honey and unique in its flavour and quality. It is a pale light runny honey with a delicate mild taste.
 £7.95 Add to Cart   Balsam Flower Honey Balsam Honey is amber coloured, it has a fairly thick consistency but will still run off a spoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Details</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Details Address:  Nook Farm, Bailey
Newcastleton
Cumbria
TD9 0TR Email:  info@nookfarmhoney.co.uk
Telephone:  01697 748317
You can contact Nook Farm Honey by Telephone, Email or by filling in the form below. If you would like to become a stockist of Nook Farm Honey, please include your phone number and address in the message window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Blossom Honey</title>
      <link>/english_spring_blossom_honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/english_spring_blossom_honey/</guid>
      <description>English Blossom Honey  English Blossom Honey is a runny honey with a clear dark golden colour it has a strong sweet taste which melts away on your tongue. The flavours come from a mix of flowers such as Lime and Apple trees, Dandelion and Hawthorn this honey is carefully and lovingly harvested from Mahmoud&amp;rsquo;s bees.
 This lovely honey is produced by Mahmoud whose apiaries are located in areas around parks, gardens and golf courses in Manchester where there is an abundance and variation of forage for the bees to gather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faqs/</guid>
      <description>FAQs   How do I order some of your honey? Use our online ordering system. Alternatively you may wish to complete our order form. You can download a copy from the website. You may want to email us, our email address is info@nookfarmhoney.co.uk This email address is being protected from spam bots, you need Javascript enabled to view it and someone will contact you back. Alternatively you can give us a call or Fax on 016977 48317.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Links British Beekeepers Association www.britishbeekeepers.com
Honey Association www.honeyassociation.com
Hives Save Lives www.hivessavelives.com
Distinctly Cumbrian www.crea.co.uk/distinctly_cumbrian.htm
CraftsAndCo.com www.craftsandco.com
Artisan Food in Cumbria www.artisan-food.com
Near Howe Self Catering Accommodation www.nearhowe.co.uk
Bees in Art www.beesinart.com
Carpe Diem Gardens www.carpe-diem-gardens.co.uk
Sugar Free Recipes www.sugarfreerecipes.co.uk/home.htm
Bee Happy Plants www.beehappyplants.co.uk
Northern Jacob Sheep www.northernjacobsheep.co.uk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Honey</title>
      <link>/our-honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-honey/</guid>
      <description>Our Honey Our honey is treated with the upmost care from the time it leaves the beehive. We filter and bottle all our honey at Nook Farm. Our honey is just fine filtered to clean the honey, nothing is added or taken away. The filter we use still allows very small particles of beeswax and pollen to remain in the honey. We believe a finer filter would remove some of the taste and beneficial properties of the honey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pure Cumbrian Wildflower Honey</title>
      <link>/pure_cumbrian_wildflower_honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pure_cumbrian_wildflower_honey/</guid>
      <description>Pure Cumbrian Wildflower Honey  Our Wildflower Honey is very runny, it is beautiful in flavour and to look at, it is truly the taste of Cumbria. This Wildflower honey has a range of flavours from the wildflowers that grow in the countryside around Nook Farm. Our Wildflower honey can vary slightly from year to year. Willow Herb, Blackberry, Clover, Thistles, Meadowsweet, and Heather all play their part in the complexity of tastes in this exclusive honey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stockists</title>
      <link>/stockists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stockists/</guid>
      <description>Stockists Download an order form or contact your local stockist
Abbey Bridge B&amp;amp;B (Lanercost Brampton )
Alston Whole Foods (Front Street, Alston, CA9 3QH )
Ashburton Village Store (21 Ashburton Road Gosforth NE3 4XN )
Beetham Nurseries (Pool Darkin Lane Milnthorpe LA7 7AP )
Bush Nook Guesthouse (Gilsland, Cumbria )
Cartmel Village Shop (The Square Cartmel Cumbria LA11 6QB )
Chestnut House (Finkle Street Pooley Bridge Penrith CA10 2NW )</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yorkshire Heather Honey</title>
      <link>/yorkshire_heather_honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/yorkshire_heather_honey/</guid>
      <description>Yorkshire Heather Honey  Our Heather honey is a smooth, rich flavoured and full bodied honey with a distinctive aroma. The initial taste is slightly caramel, and it is soon followed by a cooling sensation in the back of the mouth, it has complex aftertastes with a hint of aniseed. Heather honey needs very careful harvesting and delicate handling before it is bottled to retain all its unique natural properties. This wonderful honey is from Mark’s bees in North Yorkshire, he produces honey in batches specifically for us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>